让我们探讨一下加速器。加速器是真了不起。他们是
Let's talk about Loaders. Loaders are awesome. They were
由Honeycomb出台的，但是作为支持库的一部分却是非常有用的。
introduced in Honeycomb, but are available as part of the
所以当你要支持较老的平台版本时，
support library. So you can take advantage of them
你可以使用他们了。加速器实质上是在一个活动或者片段
when supporting earlier platform releases. Loaders are essentially the best
里实现异步数据加载最佳的实践方法。
practice implementation for asynchronous data loading within an activity
所以当你新建一个加速器的时候，他同时也在后台线程
or fragment. So when you create a Loader, it creates
创建了一个异步任务去加载数据。
an async task to load data on the background thread.
当最初的加载完成时，他就开始和用户界面线程同步了，
It then syncs with the UI thread when the initial
然后建立基础数据监听器，
loading is complete, and can be set up to monitor
并且也提供所有用户界面线程的更新。
the underlying data, and deliver any updates to the UI
好事连连，你所做的这一切
thread as well. Best still, all that work you did
通过cursor加速器为你的数据库添加一个
adding a content provider to your database pays off right
内容提供者是非常值得的。这个cursor加速器就是异步任务
now, with the cursor loader. The cursor loader is an
加速器的表现，特别是
implementation of the async task loader, specifically designed to query
可以查询内容提供者，还同时会返回一个你可以直接绑定到
content providers, and return a cursor, which you can then
一个用户界面的指针。他将自动更新指针，
bind directly to a UI. It will automatically update that cursor,
不管这个潜在的内容提供者何时改变，都是在
whenever the underlying content provider changes, based on changes
潜在的数据库的基础上改变。在一个配置发生改变之后，他将重新连接
to the underlying database. And it will reconnect to the
被重建之后最后一次返回的指针，连同着主机行为窗口
last returned cursor after being recreated, along with the
这意味着你将不需要
host activity, after a configuration change. That means you won't
重新查询数据了，就是因为这个装置是循环的。
have to requery data, just because the device was
所以这个cursor加速器解决了所有你的
rotated. So the cursor loader handles all of your cursor
指针管理还有后台线程的创建，用户界面线程的同步，还有数据源的监听。
management and background thread creation, UI thread synchronization, and data
如果你没有选择使用内容提供者，
source monitoring. If you chose not to use content providers,
那就是你的选择不佳。但至少你可以利用加速器，
you chose poorly. But still, you can take advantage
你只需要直接扩展一个think任务加速器
of loaders, you just need to create your own
就可以新建一个你自己的加速器。
loader by extending a think task loader directly. You
你会在下边的老师指导下发现更多。
can find out more in the instructor notes below.